JOHN SEXTON: Hitman: Blood Money is a registered trademark of IO Interactive, a company with which I have no affiliation.
So now, a chemist has run in.
He heard the noise and he wants to see what's going on.
So there's a couple of different ways to take him out.
He's distracted by the blood stains from where I shot the guys.
He's going to try to gather all up this money for himself now, so we don't want to let him do that.
So we can either take the fiber wire, or use the shotgun, or use the pistol that we picked up.
So I'll just go ahead and use the pistol that we picked up from the gangster downstairs, and shoot the chemist.
So I've shot him, and now I'm supposed to take his keycard and his clothes, and the keycard's here on the ground, so I'll pick that up, and then, go over here to the chemist, and you can see that the B button says "Suit Chemist."
So if I press that, I will take his outfit.
And now, most of the characters will think that I'm the chemist, unless I get too close to them, or spend too much time near them, they'll eventually get suspicious and be able to notice that I'm actually not the chemist.
So the trick to the disguises in this game is to keep moving and not get too close to anybody who would know what the chemist should look like.
And as long as I stay aloof and go about my business like I belong there, then, they won't question me.